# Latrell Sanchez

## **Professional Summary**

Highly motivated Retail Sales Associate with extensive customer service, programing and sales experience. Outgoing sales professional with track record of driving increased sales, improving buying experience and elevating company profile with target market. Consistently recognized for sales performance and excellence in customer service.

## Work History

#### Nike Inc - Athlete

Brooklyn, NY

05/2020 - Current

- Maintained store displays and followed store housekeeping standards and procedures to provide assortment of sporting goods.
- Explained details regarding current store promotions, sales and special events to customers.
- Complied with loss prevention standards and audit requirements to support retail operations.
- Performed recovery of sporting goods items and returned to specified department areas.
- Interacted with customers to provide information on different features regarding apparel and sports equipment.
- Ticketed items with pricing and mark-downs and restocked sales floor according to merchandising plan.

## Footlocker - Sales Associate

Brooklyn, NY

06/2018 - 08/2019

- Answered customer questions regarding sizing, accessories and proper care for merchandise.
- Trained and developed new hires in company processes, product knowledge, customer service and selling techniques.
- Processed product returns and assisted customers with other selections.
- Provided positive first impressions to welcome existing, new and potential customers.
- Developed, marketed and sold full range of products and support services.

➤ Sanchezlatrell30@gmail.com

**(**929)-484-6191

Prooklyn, NY 11210

#### Skills

- Sales assistance
- Apparel knowledge
- Customer engagement
- Organization
- Adaptability
- Analytical skills
- Computer skills
- Cultural awareness
- Sales trends
- Stocking and Replenishing
- Merchandising Knowledge

## Education

06/2019

## Achievement First Brooklyn High School

Brooklyn

High School Diploma

- Member of Mens JV and Variety Basketball Team
- Received Excelsior Scholarship
- Elected to Secretary for Brothers In Leadership (BIL) in 2018
- Member of Gay-Straight Alliance (GSA)

### **SUNY At Albany**

Albany, NY

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

• Achieved perfect attendance and on-time record.

## Regal Entertainment Group - Floor Usher

New York, NY 02/2018 - 05/2018

- Reviewed tickets for authenticity and applicability to particular event.
- Directed ticket holders to seats and facility locations.
- Developed and maintained courteous and effective working relationships.
- Quickly learned new skills and applied them to daily tasks, improving efficiency and productivity.
- Assisted patrons with seating by giving directions and lighting paths.

• Member of Pan Caribbean Association

05/2023

New York City College of Technology (CUNY)

Brooklyn, NY

**BA: Computer Systems** 

# **Certifications**

• IT Automation with Python, Google - 2021